kontentino.com 2018-07-06

# Privacy Policy | Kontentino

If you are a visitor to a Kontentino website or a customer of a Kontentino Service, then except as expressly set forth below, this Privacy Policy applies to your use of such Website or Service.

At Kontentino, we respect the privacy rights of our users and recognize the importance of protecting the personal information we collect about you. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand what information we collect and how we use and share that information. This Privacy Policy applies to our Websites and Services.

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

Read more in a separate article Data Policy.

## How do we protect your information?

  * Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. 
  * Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 
  * All sensitive information you supply (your phone, credit card, paypal authorization) is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

## How do we protect your billing information? (credir cards, PayPal authorization... etc)

  * _We do not store or process_ any credit card information or PayPal authorizations on our servers.   
All credit card information and PayPal authorizations are stored and processed within [Braintree Payments](https://www.braintreepayments.com/) service, known as credit card payment gate maintained by [PayPal](http://paypal.com/). 
  * Kontentino website complies with [Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)](https://articles.braintreepayments.com/reference/security/pci-compliance) and is eligible for **SAQ A** , i.e. credit card processing is full outsourced to the _Braintree Payments_ service and in Kontentino, it is provided through an iFrame. 

## Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### We use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. 

### If users disable cookies in their browser:

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

## OAuth authorizations

Kontentino uses OAuth authorization to publish content only to the social media profiles, that you allow. 

### Facebook authorizations

Kontentino requests the following permissions:

  * manage_pages
  * publish_pages
  * user_photos
  * publish_actions
  * ads_read

### Twitter authorizations

Kontentino requests `read-write` authrization from your Twitter profile.

### LinkedIn authorizations

Kontentino requests the following permissions:

  * r_basicprofile
  * rw_company_admin
  * w_share

### Google+ authorizations

Kontentino requests the following permissions:

  * https://www.googleapis.com/auth/plus.login
  * https://www.googleapis.com/auth/plus.pages.manage
  * https://www.googleapis.com/auth/plus.stream.write
  * https://www.googleapis.com/auth/plus.media.readwrite
  * https://www.googleapis.com/auth/plus.me

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being   
shared. - See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

## According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
  * **You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:**
    * Via Email
  * **Can change your personal information:**
    * By logging in to your account 

## COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

## Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**   
_We will notify you via email_

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

## CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

### We collect your email address in order to:

  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service

### To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests immediatedly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

### If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence. 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Kontentino s.r.o.  
Brigádnická 27  
841 10  Bratislava, Slovakia  
privacy@kontentino.com 

**Updated at:** 12th May, 2018
